http://www.nevisbluff.co.nz/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
This statement applies to personal information collected through www.nevisbluff.co.nz.
Collecting personal information
We do collect personal information that you choose to give us while using our website and its services, for example your email address. We only use this personal information for the purpose(s) specified at the point of collection.
Sharing your information
We do not give information about you to other organisations or anyone else unless one of the following applies:
one of the reasons we obtained the information was to give it to someone else
you have consented
it is required or authorised by the Privacy Act 1993 or by any other law.  For example, to avoid prejudice to the prevention, detection, investigation, prosecution and punishment of offences; for law enforcement; for the protection of public revenue; or for the conduct of court or tribunal proceedings
it will prevent or lessen a serious and imminent threat to public health or safety or to somebody's life or health or
the information is to be used in a way that will not identify you; or it is to be used for statistical or research purposes and will not be published in a way that will identify you.
Access to personal information we hold about you
You can ask us to give you any information that we hold about you and to make any changes to that information that you request. Contact us:
Email: raewyn@nevisbluff.co.nz
Nevis Bluff Wines Ltd, PO Box 3861, Christchurch, New Zealand
Automatic collection of information
We do not collect personal information about you if you only browse this website. We do not use cookies to store personal information. You can access and use our website with cookies disabled in your browser settings.
We - and our contractors, providers and agencies - use Google Analytics to create summary statistics that allow us to assess the number of visitors to different sections of the website, identify what information is of most and least interest, monitor system performance, and help us make our website more useful to visitors. To do this, Google Analytics collects and stores the following data when you visit the website:
Your service address (IP address)
The date, time and duration of your visit to the site
The pages you accessed and the documents you downloaded
The type of browser you used.
The Pinot Specialists...
Discover our wines
Explore our vineyard
Visit our shop
HomeOur WinesAboutThe VineyardThe WinemakerPhoto GalleryRestaurantsRestaurantsFeatured RestaurantRestaurant Ordering FormNewsContactPrivacy StatementTerms & ConditionsView Licence
Welcome
Please verify your age please
I am 18 & over
I am under 18
